Guide to the Office of the University Treasurer records, 1893-ongoing UA.10.01.0001
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
- Oversize - Unboxed Materials (housed on-site, see catalog for location), 1893-1956
  - Angier B. Duke Memorial Loan Fund, 1924-1944 (Volume 7)
  - Expendable Funds N-Z, 1924-1950 (Volume 8)
  - Loan Funds, 1915-1955 (Volume 9)
  - Loan Funds, 1945-1956 (Volume 10)
  - Monthly Charge Book, 1925-1927 (Volume 11)
  - Agency Funds/Group Investments, 1923-1955 (Volume 12)
  - Student Account Books, 1925-1926
  - Endowed-Special Endowment Funds, 1924-1954
  - Scholarship Records, 1928-1954
- Oversize - Map Cabinets
  - A.S. Brower and G.C. Henricksen subject files
    - Misc. blueprints, plans, maps, 1944-1967 (A93-102)
      - Forest Cover Map of the Durham Division, 1 July 1944 (Oversize-folder 23)
      - Property for Married Students Housing, 10 October 1961 (Oversize-folder 23)
      - Equipment Layout in Ice Plant, 28 August 1961 (Oversize-folder 23)
      - Durham County Tax Maps, 19 September 1967 (Oversize-folder 23)
      - Property of Duke University U.S. 15-501 and Morreene Road, 3 October 1967 (Oversize-folder 23)
      - Duke University Station (Oversize-folder 23)
    - Union (Trumbauer and Hackney blueprints), 1927-1929 (A93-102) (Oversize-folder 23)